Hari Sharma fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Community activism records, 1968 - 2008; F-251-3; 4.12 m of textual records
  - First Nations-SFU partnership files, 1968 - 2003; F-251-3-6; 1.38 m of textual records
    - The Third Year: A Year of Consolidation 1990-91 Annual Report - 3 copies, 1990 - 1991; F-251-3-6-0-48 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Sustainable Development, 1990 - 1991; F-251-3-6-0-49 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Shuswap research - Kamloops Bands, 1990 - 1994; F-251-3-6-0-50 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Shuswap Interviews record, 1990 - 1991; F-251-3-6-0-51 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Ron Ignace (Jan. 1990), F-251-3-6-0-52 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Eddy Jules (March 1990), F-251-3-6-0-53 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Richard Jules (Oct. 1990), F-251-3-6-0-54 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Mel Seymour (June 1990), F-251-3-6-0-55 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Rick Lebourdais (June 1990), F-251-3-6-0-56 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Nellie Taylor (Oct. 1990), F-251-3-6-0-57 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Terry Deneault (May 1990), F-251-3-6-0-58 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Comprehensive Framework Treaty, revised August 30, 1990, F-251-3-6-0-59 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - General Assembly of the Chilcotin Nation: A Declaration of Sovereignty, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-60 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Shuswap Chronicles, vol. 3, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-61 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Shuswap History: The First 100 Years of Contact, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-62 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Eddy Jules (Oct. 1991), F-251-3-6-0-63 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Manny Jules (Oct. 1991), F-251-3-6-0-64 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Robert Manuel (April 1991), F-251-3-6-0-65 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - A Household Economic Leakage Study for the Canoe Creek Indian Band, [ca 1991] - [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-66 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - A Household Economic Leakage Study for the North Thompson Band, [ca 1991] - [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-67 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Ron Ignace (Feb. 1992), F-251-3-6-0-68 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - A Study of the Employment and Expenditures of Shuswap Governments, [ca 1992] - [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-69 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - A Community Economic Development Summary Report for the Shuswap People of Adams Lake, [ca 1992] - [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-70 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Shuswap gathering programs, 1992 - 1993; F-251-3-6-0-71 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Louella Jules (April 1993), F-251-3-6-0-72 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Dorothy Jepp & Ramona Halota (July 1993), F-251-3-6-0-73 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - The Value of Cooperation: A Case Study of Six Shuswap Nation Tribal Council Communities, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-74 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Russel Casimir (April 1994), F-251-3-6-0-75 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Chief Terry Porter, Bonaparte Band (Oct. 1994), F-251-3-6-0-76 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Interview transcript: Allan Casimir, Kamloops Indian Band (March 1995), F-251-3-6-0-77 (Archival box - standard 251-43)
    - Aboriginal Suicide in British Columbia: An Executive Summary, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-78 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - B.C. Aboriginal Fisheries Commission (memo, working charter draft), 1991; F-251-3-6-0-79 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Shuswap research - Whispering Pines, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-80 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Kamloops Indian Band Audited Financial Statements, March 31, 1991, F-251-3-6-0-81 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Yinka Dene Language Institute: Developing Aboriginal Studies Discussion Paper, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-82 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Sek'lep School Evaluation, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-83 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Impact of the Residential School, Cariboo Tribal Council, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-84 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Memo regarding Delgamuukw v. The Queen: Summary of Judgment, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-85 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Western Social Policy Forum: Treaty making and nation building, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-86 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - The Report of the British Columbia Task Force, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-87 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Secwepemc Native Community College: A Three Year Operational Plan for the Secwepmc Cultural Education Society, 1991; F-251-3-6-0-88 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - SSHRC - Grant(ed) Shuswap proposal, 1991 - 1992; F-251-3-6-0-89 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - SSHRC - Proposal, 1991 - 1992; F-251-3-6-0-90 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Interim Measures, Report on Land Claims Task Force, 1991 - 1992; F-251-3-6-0-91 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - Shuswap Nation Tribal Council Political/Technical Working Group Meeting, 1991 - 1994; F-251-3-6-0-92 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - SSHRC correspondence, applications, memos, 1991 - 1995; F-251-3-6-0-93 (Archival box - standard 251-44)
    - The Shuswap (Secwepemc) by Marianne Boelscher Ignace, 1992; F-251-3-6-0-94 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Shuswap Nation Tribal Council Chiefs' council meeting - August 12, 1992, F-251-3-6-0-95 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Discussion Paper 1: Framing the Issues, Royal Commission on Aboriginal Peoples, 1992; F-251-3-6-0-96 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Public Hearings: Overview of the First Round, Royal Commission on Aboriginal Peoples, 1992; F-251-3-6-0-97 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Proposal Structure of Shuswap Fisheries Commission, [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-98 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - GIS and information systems, [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-99 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Introduction to the Shuswap: Shuswap Cultural Series Book 1, [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-100 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - An Addendum Proposal for the National Aboriginal Management Board, [ca 1992] - [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-101 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Northern Research and Education at Yukon College newsletter, vol. 2, no. 2, 1992; F-251-3-6-0-102 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Nisga'a: People of the mighty river (booklet), 1992; F-251-3-6-0-103 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - A Guide to Indian Affairs in British Columbia, [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-104 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Native Justice Proposal by Kamloops Indian Band, prepared by Cora Anthony, 1992; F-251-3-6-0-105 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Maps of sovereign Indigenous Nations' territorial boundaries, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-106 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Celia/Kelleen project - Cariboo Bands, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-107 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society - personnel list, 1993; F-251-3-6-0-108 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - The Cost of Mistrust: A Case Study of the Shuswap People of Kamloops, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-109 (Archival box - standard 251-45)
    - A Model for Sustainable Watershed Management in Traditional Shuswap Territory - SFU-MRM report no. 8, 1992; F-251-3-6-0-110 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - A Community Economic Development Study for The Kamloops Indian Band, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-111 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - A Community Economic Development Summary Report for the Shuswap People of Bonaparte, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-112 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - A Community Economic Development Summary Report for the Shuswap People of Skeetchestn, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-113 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - A Model for Cooperation Between the Shuswap People of Kamloops & the Businesses of the Mount Paul Industrial Park, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-114 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - A Brief Tax (on a me) of First Nations Taxation and Economic Development, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-115 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - A Preliminary Evaluation of the Tax Base of the Westbank First Nation, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-116 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Community Economic Development and New Community Project Land Base Survey, High Bar Band, 1993; F-251-3-6-0-117 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Presentation to Employment and Immigration Canada on Development of an Education and Employment Database Program, [ca 1993]; F-251-3-6-0-118 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - The Mysterious Trail of Suspect Statistics: A Case Study of Five Shuswap Nation Tribal Council Communities, 1993; F-251-3-6-0-119 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - KIB Family Groupings, 1993; F-251-3-6-0-120 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - SFU's Secwepemc Credit Programs brochure, 1993; F-251-3-6-0-121 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - National Advisory Council on Indian Education (NACIE) newsletter - vol. 9, no. 2, 1993; F-251-3-6-0-122 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Shuswap research - general, 1989 - 1994; F-251-3-6-0-123 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Shastri-Bhopal - R. Anderson, 1993 - 1996; F-251-3-6-0-124 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Interim Measures Strategic Plan: From the Current Situation to Post-Treaty, [ca 1994]; F-251-3-6-0-125 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Gaul, Thomas: Indigenous Perspectives: Ecology, Economy and Ethics, [199-]; F-251-3-6-0-126 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Sechelt Indian Band Land Claims Information Package, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-127 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Spallumcheen - Cindy Williams (notes), 1994; F-251-3-6-0-128 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - KIB voters list, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-129 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Community profile: Shuswap Nation - research outline, [ca 1994]; F-251-3-6-0-130 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Canadian Association for Distance Education Association: Some programs for northern and native communities offered at a distance, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-131 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - The Provincial Land Use Strategy Volume 1: A Sustainability Act for British Columbia, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-132 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Treaty News (Vol. 1, No. 2), 1994; F-251-3-6-0-133 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Draft training proposal - First Nations Lands and Environmental Resource Management, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-134 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Coyote Times (SCES/SFU Program Newsletters: February 1994), F-251-3-6-0-135 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Draft proposal: Science and Technology Pilot Program for Schools of Inland Fisheries, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-136 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Draft paper for CAUCE Journal re. SFU and Secwepemc First Nations Studies program, 1994; F-251-3-6-0-137 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Correspondence and articles for lecture given by H. Sharma on addiction from sociological POV, [ca 1994]; F-251-3-6-0-138 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - SSHRC Research, 1994 - 1995; F-251-3-6-0-139 (Archival box - standard 251-46)
    - Bonaparte Band, [ca 1994]; F-251-3-6-0-140 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Papers of the Learned, [ca 1994] - [ca 1995]; F-251-3-6-0-141 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - The David Suzuki Foundation Fish on the Line: The Future of Pacific Fisheries, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-142 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Getting the Missing Fish Story Straight, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-143 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - SCES meeting: Kamloops - notes, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-144 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Coyote Times: The SCES-SFU University Program Newsletter, 1995 - 1997; F-251-3-6-0-145 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Misc. correspondence, articles, notes re. aboriginal land, research, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-146 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - SCES/SFU funding, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-147 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Shuswap research notes, [ca 1995]; F-251-3-6-0-148 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Shuswap project financial data - budget summary paperwork, correspondence, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-149 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Learned Societies Conference - Annual Meeting program, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-150 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Joining Hands: A University Enters a 'Partnership' with a First Nations People, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-151 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Environment and First Nations (notes, bulletins, email forwards), 1995; F-251-3-6-0-152 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Shuswap mis. Field notes, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-153 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - SCES/SFU program report sent by Ruth Epstein, 1995; F-251-3-6-0-154 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - Treaty negotiation, [ca 1995]; F-251-3-6-0-155 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - First Nations - resources, newsletters, research, 1995 - 1997; F-251-3-6-0-156 (Archival box - standard 251-47)
    - SCES/SFU research, project administration, planning, 1995 - 1998; F-251-3-6-0-157 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Research grants division final productivity report, notes, correspondence, 1996; F-251-3-6-0-158 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Symposium 96: An Indigenous Celebration - "Belonging to the Earth: Indigenous Wisdom, Cultural Identity and Human Rights", 1996; F-251-3-6-0-159 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - SCES/SFU Convocation Ceremony, 1996; F-251-3-6-0-160 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Annotated bibliography - Aboriginal lands research, [ca 1996]; F-251-3-6-0-161 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Anderson - complaint, 1991 - 1997; F-251-3-6-0-162 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Land stewardship training program material, 1997; F-251-3-6-0-163 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Misconduct of research allegations - correspondence, reports, 1997; F-251-3-6-0-164 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Shuswap maps, [ca 1987] - [ca 1995]; F-251-3-6-0-165 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Correspondence between Dr. Marianne Ignace and BC Hydro re. Aboriginal lands, resource, and environmental management program, 1987; F-251-3-6-0-166 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - SCES/SFU research, planning, 1997 - 1998; F-251-3-6-0-167 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society/SFU convocation program and graduation list, 1998; F-251-3-6-0-168 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Speaking notes on SCES/SFU program prepared by Hari Sharma, 1998; F-251-3-6-0-169 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - SCES/SFU tenth anniversary report - foreword, 1998; F-251-3-6-0-170 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - SCES/SFU - Tenth anniversary, 1998; F-251-3-6-0-171 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - A Guide to Aboriginal Organizations and Services in British Columbia 1998, F-251-3-6-0-172 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - SCES/SFU joint committee minutes, course listings, etc., 2001; F-251-3-6-0-173 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
    - Letter of support to nominate Dr. Marianne Ignace for the YWCA Woman of Distinction Award, 2003; F-251-3-6-0-174 (Archival box - standard 251-48)
  - Komagata Maru Historical Society files, 1988 - 2008; F-251-3-7; 13 cm of textual records; Komagata Maru Historical Society
    The Komagata Maru Historical Society was a coalition of South Asian community-based organizations formed in 1989. The event commemorated the 75th anniversary of the Komagata Maru incident in which Indian immigrants traveling to Canada on a chartered ship were turned away from the shores of Vancouver due to racist policies of the government.
    Sub-series consists of administrative records of the Komagata Maru Historical Society that were kept by Hari Sharma while he was President of the society. Records relate to research, education, funding, and publicity of commemorative events marking the 75th anniversary of the 1914 Komagata Maru incident. Sub-series consists of newspaper clippings, correspondence, minutes, brochures, photographs, letterheads, notes, emails, and some financial records.
    Komagata Maru Historical Society; Textual records
    - Komagata Maru (clippings), 1988 - 1989; F-251-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Komagata Maru: Khalsa Diwan Society, 1989; F-251-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Komagata Maru: Nov. 5 ticket sales, 1989; F-251-3-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Komagata Maru Curriculum, 1989; F-251-3-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Souvenir Brochure (correspondence, photos), 1989; F-251-3-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Correspondence: other groups/personalities, 1989; F-251-3-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Finances, 1989; F-251-3-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Letters after Nov. 5 event, 1989; F-251-3-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Contacts, 1989 - 1990; F-251-3-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Proclamations / Plaques, 1989 - 1990; F-251-3-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1989 - 1990; F-251-3-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Montreal Serai, 1989 - 1990; F-251-3-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Founding of society, stationary, documents, 1990; F-251-3-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
    - Komagata Maru - campaigns, events, notes, documents, emails, etc., 2005 - 2008; F-251-3-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-49)
- Research files, 1976 - 2009; F-251-4; 1.25 m of textual records
  Series consists of records arising from Sharma's research activities and conference participation. Series includes correspondence, research articles, notes, and other materials.
  The arrangement was provided by the archivist and is based on subjects documented in the records. Files are arranged chronologically.
  - Political research files, 1976 - 2009; F-251-4-1; 25 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records compiled by Hari Sharma to support his political research interests. Research subjects covered in these records include Third World politics, India, China, Philippines, Soviet Union, Cambodia, and other topics. Sub-series includes notes, bibliographies, student papers, articles, contact lists, resource lists, and citations.
    Files are open with no access restrictions.
    - Songs (revolutionary music), 1976 - 1987; F-251-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Notes from sociology and anthropology seminar: The Social Contraints of Perestroika, 1989; F-251-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Soviet Union and Afghanistan - report by work-study student, 1990; F-251-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Soviet Union: Statistics, by Kathryn Rockwell, 1990; F-251-4-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - The Soviet Union: An Annotated Bibliography, by Kathryn Rockwell, 1990; F-251-4-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Student paper: From Khrushchev to Brezhnev: The Evolution of Soviet-Cuban Relations, 1991; F-251-4-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - China/3rd World/Analysis/USSR: Restoration of Capitalism, 1992 - 2007; F-251-4-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - M-L Notes - Misc./Europe, 1992 - 2000; F-251-4-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Kampuchea (notes, articles), 1993 - 2007; F-251-4-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Contacts, etc., 1995 - 1999; F-251-4-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Philippines, 1995 - 2005; F-251-4-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Untouchables, 1996; F-251-4-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - Web sites to check (notes, clippings, emails), 1997 - 1999; F-251-4-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-50)
    - References and notes, 1998 - 2001; F-251-4-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Writing notes, 1998 - 2001; F-251-4-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - USA/Bully/Global/Economic Issues, 1998 - 2002; F-251-4-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Vancouver Anti-War Coalition, 1999 - 2001; F-251-4-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - 9-11-01: America Under Attack, 2001 - 2002; F-251-4-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Religion (book citations, titles), 2003; F-251-4-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Third World - Pakistan/Vietnam/Cambodia, [ca 2003] - [ca 2006]; F-251-4-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Fiction, [ca 2006]; F-251-4-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - China/Russia Communism, etc. (book titles), [ca 2007]; F-251-4-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Capitalism/Imperialism/Glozation, etc. (book titles), [ca 2007] - [ca 2008]; F-251-4-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - Terror Lists (Re. U.S. politics), 2008; F-251-4-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
    - China Symposium: Mao and Post-Mao periods, 2009; F-251-4-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 251-51)
  - Race relations research files, 1978 - 1989; F-251-4-2; 38 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records compiled by Hari Sharma as a member of the City of Vancouver's Police/Ethnic Liaison Committee and Special Committee on Race Relations. Sub-series includes papers, notes, correspondence, minutes, newsletters, and memos.
    Vancouver Special Committee on Race Relations; Vancouver Police Department; Textual records
    - Racism research - copies of other researchers' papers, notes, correspondence, 1978 - 1987; F-251-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-52)
    - Special Council Committee on Race Relations (Vancouver), 1982 - 1983; F-251-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-52)
    - For Police/Ethnic Liaison Committee Members from Charles Umgerleider, [ca 1983]; F-251-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-52)
    - Police/Ethnic Liaison Committee, VPD, 1983 - 1984; F-251-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-52)
    - Multicultural Theatre, 1984; F-251-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-53)
    - Race Relations Committee, 1984; F-251-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-53)
    - Equality Now, 1984; F-251-4-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-53)
    - House of Commons Special Committee on Visible Minorities, 1984; F-251-4-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-53)
    - BC Police Committee: Selection Procedures, [ca 1984] - [ca 1985]; F-251-4-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-53)
    - Race Relations Committee, 1985; F-251-4-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-53)
    - Media and Race Relations, 1985 - 1986; F-251-4-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-54)
    - Vancouver City Hall Employees, 1985 - 1987; F-251-4-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-54)
    - Police - Ethnic Committee, 1985 - 1987; F-251-4-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-54)
    - Race Relations - 1986, 1986 - 1987; F-251-4-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-54)
    - South Africa Anti-Apartheid Network, 1987; F-251-4-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-54)
    - Coalition 33, 1989; F-251-4-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-54)
  - Conference and seminar notes, lectures, and proceedings, 1979 - 2006; F-251-4-3; 26 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records arising from Hari Sharma's participation in various conferences and seminars relating to his political and research interests, particularly relating to Marxism, Maoism, communalism, and other revolutionary models. Sub-series includes correspondence, notes, articles, essays, agendas, conference proceedings, planning materials, and other materials.